The Professionals is a crime, thriller film directed by Don Sharp.
A renowned safecracker and his crew try to rob a bank by
entering the vault through the sewer system.
Philip Bowman, played by William Lucas.
Inspector Rankin, played by Andrew Faulds.
Ruth, played by Colette Wilde.
Lawson, played by Stratford Johns.
Mabel, played by Vilma Ann Leslie.
Clayton, played by Edward Cast.
The Professionals is a 1960 British crime thriller, directed by Don Sharp
and starring William Lucas, Andrew Faulds and Colette Wilde.
It screened on US television in 1961 as part of
the Kraft Mystery Theatre series.
It was one of a series of films Anglo-Amalgamated sold to
US television for one million dollars.
The tone is intense.